Guide to the Jack Gelber Papers 1938-2002 (Bulk 1957-1999) MSS.146
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Subseries A
    - Saint Clement's, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 565)
    - Saint John's University, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 566)
    - Saks, Gene, Undated (Box 10, Folder 567)
    - Salisbury, Leah, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 568)
    - Sam, Philip, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 569)
    - Samuel French, Inc., 1963 (Box 10, Folder 570)
      See Also: Fratti, Mario (Series IA, Box 4, Folder 229), Konecky, Ronald S. (Series IA, Box 6, Folder 344)
    - Sanctuary Theatre Workshop, Undated (Box 10, Folder 571)
    - San Francisco Art Institute, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 572)
    - San Jose Repertory Theatre, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 573)
    - Sater, Steven E., 1979 (Box 10, Folder 574)
    - The Saturday Evening Post, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 575)
    - Saturday Review Press, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 576)
    - Scates, Suzanne, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 577)
    - Schenectady Community College, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 578)
    - Schlesinger, John, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 579)
    - Schreibman, Barry, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 580)
    - Scott-Fox, Judy, 1966-1973 (Box 10, Folder 581)
    - Screen Actors Guild, Inc., 1987 (Box 10, Folder 582)
      The contents of this folder include a signed "Daily Contract (Day Player) for Theatrical Motion Pictures" and a portion of the script for Woody Allen's film Another Woman
    - Seattle Repertory Theatre, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 583)
    - Seaver, Jeannette Seaver, Richard, 1961-1977 (Box 10, Folder 584)
    - The Second Stage, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 585)
    - Semones, Karon, 1993-1997 (Box 10, Folder 586)
      This folder also holds letters from Gurney Norman and Jonathan Greene (Gnomon Press)
    - Serra, Chime, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 587)
    - Seybold, John, Undated (Box 10, Folder 588)
    - Seymour Goldes Certified Public Accountant, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 589)
    - Seyrio, Coralie, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 590)
    - S. Fischer Verlag, Theaterabteilung, 1969-1974 (Box 10, Folder 591)
    - [Shai], Martin, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 592)
    - Sheffer, Ethel Sheffer, Isaiah, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 593)
    - Shepard, Sam, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 594)
      See Also: "Seduced" by Sam Shepard, Two Photocopies of Annotated Scripts for Act 1 with an Annotated Typescript for Act 2 (Series IIP, Box 37, Folder 1074)
    - Sheppard, Morgan, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 595)
    - Sherman, Ellen Stacey, Undated (Box 10, Folder 596)
    - Sherman, Jules, Undated (Box 10, Folder 597)
    - Shirey, Linda D., 1985 (Box 10, Folder 598)
    - Show: The Magazine of the Arts, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 599)
      See Also: "By the Way, My Name is Roger Soames" (Typescript and Two Pages from a Handwritten Version) (Series IIR, Box 42, Folder 1129)
    - Shull, Dick, Undated (Box 10, Folder 600)
    - Shulman, Jacobson, and Company Certified Public Accountants, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 601)
    - Siegel, Robert, Undated (Box 10, Folder 602)
      See Also: Ari, Mark (Series 1A Box 1 Folder 28)
    - Sievers, Devera, Undated (Box 10, Folder 603)
    - Silver, Tracey, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 604)
    - Simon and Garfunkel, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 605)
    - Simon, Roger Hendricks, 1972-1983 (Box 10, Folder 606)
    - Simon-Ross, Celia, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 607)
    - Simon, S.W., 1963 (Box 10, Folder 608)
    - [Slaff], Jerry, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 609)
    - Smalley, Webster, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 610)
    - Smith College, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 611)
    - Smith, Toni, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 612)
    - Snow, Joe Snow, Miriam, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 613)
    - Sociedade Brasileira de Autores Teatrais, 1970-1984 (Box 10, Folder 614)
    - Sociedade Portuguesa de Autores, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 615)
    - Societe des Auteurs et Compositeurs Dramatiques, 1968-1997 (Box 10, Folder 616)
    - Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers, Inc., 1973-1990 (Box 10, Folder 617)
    - Soloman R. Guggenheim Museum, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 618)
    - SOPE Hellas, Copyright Protection Society, 1983-1999 (Box 10, Folder 619)
    - Sottsass, Fernanda Pivano, 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 620)
    - Southwest Theatre Conference, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 621)
    - Spar, Lilah Spar, Nat, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 622)
    - Spear, Nat, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 623)
    - Spicer, James, Undated (Box 10, Folder 624)
    - Spielburg, David, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 625)
    - Spielburg, Peter, 1990, Undated (Box 10, Folder 626)
      See Also: The Rockefeller Foundation (Series IA, Box 9, Folder 547)
    - Spiro, Peter, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 627)
    - Stables Theatre Club, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 628)
    - Stadsteatern Stockholm, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 629)
    - Starer, Robert, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 630)
    - State of New York, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 631)
    - State University College (Geneseo, NY), 1964 (Box 11, Folder 632)
    - State University of New York at Albany, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 633)
    - State University of New York at Stony Brook, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 634)
    - Stebner, Gerhard, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 635)
    - Stein, Howard, 1974-1989 (Box 11, Folder 636)
    - Steinman, Robert, Undated (Box 11, Folder 637)
    - Stern, Daniel, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 638)
    - Steve Yeager Films, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 639)
    - Stichting tot Exploitatie en Bescherming van Auteursrechten (SEBA), 1970-1974 (Box 11, Folder 640)
    - Stoudt, Paul, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 641)
    - Streisand Center for Jewish Cultural Arts at the University of California-Los Angeles, [1987] (Box 11, Folder 642)
    - Student Experimental Theatre, Arizona State University, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 643)
    - Studio 10,001, Inc., 1963 (Box 11, Folder 644)
    - Studies in American Drama, 1945-Present, 1987-1997 (Box 11, Folder 645)
    - Studio Arena Theatre, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 646)
    - Stunda, Susie, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 647)
    - Sun Valley Center for the Arts, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 648)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IA Oversize, Box 48, Folder 1194
    - Syracuse Stage, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 649)
    - Syron, Bryan, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 650)
    - Tabac Rhein, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 651)
    - [Tabin, Liatt], 1987 (Box 11, Folder 652)
    - Tammany, Susan, Undated (Box 11, Folder 653)
    - Tantleff, Jack, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 654)
    - Taylor, Karen Malpede, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 655)
    - Taylor, Thomas J., 1983 (Box 11, Folder 656)
    - Teaterforlaget SCALA, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 657)
      See Also: Arlecchino Teaterforlag Bertil Boden (Series IA, Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Temporary Assistance for Women, Undated (Box 11, Folder 658)
    - Tenenbaum, Tuvia, 1988-1994 (Box 11, Folder 659)
    - Terry, Megan, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 660)
    - Theatre Arts Division, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 661)
    - Theatre by the Sea, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 662)
    - Theatre Communications Group, Inc., 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 663)
    - Theatre de la Jeune Lune, [1990] (Box 11, Folder 664)
    - Theatre Gerard Phillipe, Undated (Box 11, Folder 665)
    - Thibeau, Jack, 1984, Undated (Box 11, Folder 666)
    - Thorn, Eric P., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 667)
    - [Tiai, Tauria], Undated (Box 11, Folder 668)
    - Titus Productions, Inc., 1981 (Box 11, Folder 669)
    - Tombach, Irving, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 670)
    - Topenoff, Rufe, Undated (Box 11, Folder 671)
    - Toronto Free Theatre, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 672)
    - Torres, Maria Elena, 1980-1988 (Box 11, Folder 673)
    - Towbin, Marion Fredi, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 674)
    - Traverse Theatre Club, Undated (Box 11, Folder 675)
      See Also: Rudman, Michael (Series IA, Box 9, Folder 557)
    - Trinity Square Repertory Company, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 676)
    - Triplett, William, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 677)
    - Tufts University, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 678)
    - Twain, Norman, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 679)
    - Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 680)
      See Also: Wigan, Gareth (Series IA, Box 12, Folder 726)
    - Tynan, Kathleen, 1980-1988 (Box 11, Folder 681)
    - Tynan, Kenneth, 1962-1969 (Box 11, Folder 682)
    - Tzavta Center for Progressive Culture, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 683)
    - Ubulibri, 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 684)
    - United States Department of the Army, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 685)
    - United States Department of State, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 686)
    - United States Department of the Treasury, 1964-1967 (Box 11, Folder 687)
    - Universal Movement Theatre Repertory, Undated (Box 11, Folder 688)
    - University of Charleston, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 689)
    - University of Hawaii, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 690)
    - University of Mississippi, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 691)
      See Also: Crews, John (Series IA, Box 3, Folder 156)
    - University of Wyoming, 1969-1973 (Box 11, Folder 692)
    - Ure, Mary, Undated (Box 11, Folder 693)
    - [Uria], Fernando, Undated (Box 11, Folder 694)
    - Urizen Books, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 695)
    - Utopian Communities in America Film Project, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 696)
    - V., Ellen, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 697)
    - Varip Brazilian Airlines, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 698)
    - Viking Press, Inc., 1974 (Box 12, Folder 699)
    - The Village Vanguard, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 700)
    - The Village Voice, 1973, Undated (Box 12, Folder 701)
    - Villa Julie College, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 702)
    - Vinaver, Steve Winchell, Walter, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 703)
    - Vincent, Glyn, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 704)
    - W., Arnaldo, Undated (Box 12, Folder 705)
    - Walden, Steu, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 706)
    - Wallach, Ira, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 707)
    - Walsh, Jim, 1969-1979, Undated (Box 12, Folder 708)
    - Wang, Pu-Ching, Undated (Box 12, Folder 709)
    - Wangh, Steve, 1979-1985 (Box 12, Folder 710)
    - Wanshel, Jeff, 1983-1987 (Box 12, Folder 711)
    - Warland, G.E.J., 1961 (Box 12, Folder 712)
    - Warner, Elizabeth, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 713)
    - Washington University in St. Louis, 1984-1991 (Box 12, Folder 714)
      See Also: "Starters" (Bound Annotated Typescript) and Notes (Series II,I, Box 27, Folder 985)
    - WCBS-TV, 1959, Undated (Box 12, Folder 715)
    - [Weber, Mike], 1959 (Box 12, Folder 716)
    - Weiner, Edward Randall, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 717)
    - Weinrib, Len, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 718)
    - Weinstein, Arnold, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 719)
    - Weinstein, Michael, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 720)
    - Weissman, Wolff, Bergman, Coleman, and Schulman, A Law Partnership, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 721)
      This folder also holds a letter from the Jayne Development Corporation
    - Wesker, Arnold, 1965-1971 (Box 12, Folder 722)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 723)
    - Whittier, Lee, Undated (Box 12, Folder 724)
    - Whittlesey, Peregrine, 1981-1989, Undated (Box 12, Folder 725)
      The contents of this folder include copies of outgoing letters to various producers and theatre directors
    - Wigan, Gareth, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 726)
    - Wiggins, Jim, [1965] (Box 12, Folder 727)
    - Wilcox, Agnes, 1980-1990, Undated (Box 12, Folder 728)
    - Williams Center Repertory Theatre, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 729)
    - Williams, Charlie K., 1996 (Box 12, Folder 730)
    - Williams, Galen, 1972-1978 (Box 12, Folder 731)
    - Williams, K., 1998 (Box 12, Folder 732)
    - Wilmurt, Arthur, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 733)
    - Wisconsin Center for Theatre Research, 1964-1970 (Box 12, Folder 734)
    - Wittman, Wolfgang, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 735)
    - Wolk, Andy, 1970-1974 (Box 12, Folder 736)
    - Wollheim, Richard, 1960, Undated (Box 12, Folder 737)
    - Woodie King Associates, Inc., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 738)
    - The Working Theatre, Undated (Box 12, Folder 739)
    - Writers and Artists Agency, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 740)
    - Writers Guild of America East, Inc., 1973-1994 (Box 12, Folder 741)
      This folder also holds a missive from the Trouts Drama Club of University of Technology, Sydney; See Also: Shulman, Jacobson, and Company Certified Public Accountants (Series IA, Box 10, Folder 601)
    - [Wulp], John, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 742)
    - Wysocki, David, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 743)
    - Yale Repertory Theatre, 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 744)
    - Yale/Theatre Magazine, 1975-1977, Undated (Box 12, Folder 745)
    - Yale University, 1974-1992 (Box 12, Folder 746)
      See Also: Brustein, Robert (Series IA, Box 2, Folder 95); Gassner, John (Series IA, Box 4, Folder 241)
    - Yale University Films, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 747)
      The contents of this folder include letters from Media Design Studio Productions, Inc. and a copy of a signed contract for a screenplay, to be written by Gelber, regarding Adolf Sutro
    - Yale University Media Design Studio, 1977, Undated (Box 12, Folder 748)
      See Also: Yale University Films (Series IA, Box 12, Folder 747)
    - Yglesias, Don, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 749)
    - Yoken, Melvin B., 1972-1991 (Box 12, Folder 750)
    - Yorck, Ruth, 1961-1965 (Box 12, Folder 751)
    - Zajc, Dave, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 752)
    - Zeeb, John, Undated (Box 12, Folder 753)
    - Zodiac Associates Productions, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 754)
  - Subseries B: One Name Only
    - Al, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 755)
    - Alan, Undated (Box 13, Folder 756)
      The contents of this folder include a clipping of "Gelber Maintains Tough View of Life," by William Glover, Associated Press, Undated
    - Alex, 1968-1996 (Box 13, Folder 757)
      The contents of this folder include a clipping of "Reedition de 'The Connection' film phare de l'ecole de New York'" by Jacques Mandelbaum, Le Monde, December 13, 1996.
    - Alex Marianne, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 758)
    - Andie, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 759)
    - Anne, Undated (Box 13, Folder 760)
    - Annette Jon, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 761)
    - Arthur, 1965-1972 (Box 13, Folder 762)
      The contents of this folder include a clipping of "The Random House-Grove Press Imbroglio," Publisher's Weekly, November 27, 1972
    - Avi, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 763)
    - Babs, 1983, Undated (Box 13, Folder 764)
    - Barbara, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 765)
    - Bellwoods, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 766)
    - Bob, Undated (Box 13, Folder 767)
    - Brad, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 768)
    - Brian Elizabeth, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 769)
    - Brownie, Undated (Box 13, Folder 770)
    - Burke, Undated (Box 13, Folder 771)
    - Carmen Richard, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 772)
    - Carol, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 773)
    - Caroline Frank, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 774)
    - C.E., Undated (Box 13, Folder 775)
      The contents of this folder include a clipping of "Very Far Off Broadway but True to the Spirit," Bruce Weber, The New York Times, June 29, 1999
    - Ceal, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 776)
    - Cecelia, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 777)
    - Cleo, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 778)
    - Dan, 1986-1987, Undated (Box 13, Folder 779)
    - [Dalvn], Undated (Box 13, Folder 780)
      The contents of this folder include a clipping of "Beatnik on the Borderline," Victor Hughes, Cape Times, April 7, 1965
    - David, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 781)
    - Deborah, 1983-1986 (Box 13, Folder 782)
    - Debra, Undated (Box 13, Folder 783)
      The contents of this folder include a clipping of "Born Guilty," [Theatre Work], Undated
    - Dick, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 784)
      This folder also holds a copy of Metronome Volume 78, Number 7 (July 1961), (New York: The Metronome Corporation, 1961)
    - D.P., Undated (Box 13, Folder 785)
    - Em Kay, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 786)
    - Emily, Undated (Box 13, Folder 787)
    - Fred, Undated (Box 13, Folder 788)
    - Gaby, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 789)
    - Gaby Jerry, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 790)
    - Galen, Undated (Box 13, Folder 791)
      The contents of this folder include a clipping of "Machiavellian Machinations," Unknown Author, American Theatre Volume 3, Number 11 (February 1987)
    - Gaynor, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 792)
    - George, Undated (Box 13, Folder 793)
    - Gerald, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 794)
    - Hal, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 795)
    - Harold, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 796)
    - Ines, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 797)
      See Also: Wysocki, David (Series IA, Box 12, Folder 743)
    - [Jacs], Undated (Box 13, Folder 798)
    - Jane Sam, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 799)
    - Jenny, Undated (Box 13, Folder 800)
    - Jerry, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 801)
    - Jess, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 802)
    - Jim, Undated (Box 13, Folder 803)
      The message is written on a clipping of "Revisiting the Hiss Case," by Hilton Kramer, Unknown Publication, Undated
    - Jim Judith Julian, Undated (Box 13, Folder 804)
    - Jo Ann, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 805)
    - Joanne, Undated (Box 13, Folder 806)
    - Jon, 1974-1978 (Box 13, Folder 807)
    - Joy, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 808)
    - Judy, 1965-1997 (Box 13, Folder 809)
    - Kath, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 810)
    - Ken, 1969-1989 (Box 13, Folder 811)
      The contents of this folder include a clipping: "'The Apple' Plotless, Imaginative Drama," Margaret Harford, Los Angeles Times, July 31, 1962
    - Keneas, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 812)
    - Kim, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 813)
    - Leonardo Roberta, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 814)
    - Lew, Undated (Box 13, Folder 815)
    - Lore, Undated (Box 13, Folder 816)
    - Lucille, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 817)
    - M, Undated (Box 13, Folder 818)
    - Marianne, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 819)
    - Marion, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 820)
    - Mark, Undated (Box 14, Folder 821)
    - Martin, Undated (Box 14, Folder 822)
    - Melinda, 1997, Undated (Box 14, Folder 823)
      The contents of this folder include a clipping of "'Sleep: an Experiment' by Jack Gelber," unknown author, unknown publication, 1997
    - Merielle, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 824)
    - Michael, Undated (Box 14, Folder 825)
    - Mickey, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 826)
    - Mike, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 827)
    - Mildred Steve, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 828)
      The contents of this folder include a clipping of "Select Crowd," by Frank DiGiacomo and Timothy McDarrah, New York Post, August 16, 1990
    - M.L.R., 1985 (Box 14, Folder 829)
    - Morry, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 830)
    - Nicholas, Undated (Box 14, Folder 831)
    - Nina, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 832)
    - N.M. R.L., 1968 (Box 14, Folder 833)
    - Nora, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 834)
    - Oswaldo, Undated (Box 14, Folder 835)
    - Patricia, Undated (Box 14, Folder 836)
    - Paul, Undated (Box 14, Folder 837)
    - Percy, Undated (Box 14, Folder 838)
    - [Perry], 1985 (Box 14, Folder 839)
    - Peter, 1961-1980, Undated (Box 14, Folder 840)
    - Peter Wendy, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 841)
    - Previto, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 842)
    - Rob, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 843)
      The contents of this folder include a clipping of "Indignacion Popular en Casilda por la Agresion," Aldo Isidron del Valle and Mario Ferrer, Revolucion, February 6, 1965
    - Robbin, Undated (Box 14, Folder 844)
    - Roger, Undated (Box 14, Folder 845)
    - Ron, 1961, Undated (Box 14, Folder 846)
    - Rose, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 847)
    - Roylan, Undated (Box 14, Folder 848)
    - Sam, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 849)
    - Sidney, Undated (Box 14, Folder 850)
    - Stan, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 851)
      The contents of this folder include a clipping of "Farewell to a Tom Paine," Jerry Tallmer, New York Post, September 21, 1985
    - Susan, 1998, Undated (Box 14, Folder 852)
    - Susana, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 853)
    - Susie, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 854)
    - Suzanne, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 855)
    - Sy, Undated (Box 14, Folder 856)
    - Teddy, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 857)
    - Turk, Undated (Box 14, Folder 858)
    - Verna, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 859)
    - Wendy, Undated (Box 14, Folder 860)
    - Winston, [1994] (Box 14, Folder 861)
    - Wolfgang, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 862)
    - [W.W.], Undated (Box 14, Folder 863)
    - [W.X.], Undated (Box 14, Folder 864)
    - Unsigned, 1960-1983, Undated (Box 14, Folder 865)
      The contents of this folder include a clipping of "'The Connection' Film Dealing With Dope Addiction, Is Coming Wednesday to Crescent Art Theatre," The Courier Journal, Louisville, Kentucky, February 10, 1963 along with page from Who's Who in American Jewry, (New York: Jewish Biographical Bureau, c1927-); See Also: "Starters, Tues 4/6/82 Latest Revision" (Annotated Typescript) and Notes (Series II,I, Box 28, Folder 992)
  - Subseries C: Biographical Clippings, Ticket Stubs, and Receipts
    - Biographical Clippings, 1968-1999, Undated (Box 14, Folder 866)
      For Oversize Materials See: Series IC Oversize, Box 48, Folder 1195
    - Receipts, 1966, Undated (Box 14, Folder 867)
    - Ticket Stubs and Post Office Receipt, 1977-1994, Undated (Box 14, Folder 868)
- Series II: Production Files
  - Subseries A: The Connection
    - "The Living Theatre" (Notes), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 869)
    - Bound Photocopies of a Flyer and Reviews, 1959-1960 (Box 15, Folder 870)
    - "The Connection: A Play in Two Acts" (Annotated Typescript), 1957 (Box 15, Folder 871)
    - "The Connection: A Play in Two Acts" (Typescript), 1957 (Box 15, Folder 872)
      This script was transferred from Fales American Box to the Jack Gelber Papers on April 15, 2005
    - "'O Contato' de Jack Gelber, Traducao de Ana Edler e Jack Brown" (Typescript), 1961 (Box 15, Folder 873)
    - "'Le Pour Voyeur,' Adaptation Francaise d'Alain Brunet" (Typescript), Undated (Box 15, Folder 874)
    - Journal Entries (Typescript), Undated (Box 15, Folder 875)
    - Notebook, Undated (Box 15, Folder 876)
    - "The Camden Jazz Festival," Advertisements and Hampstead Theatre Club Program, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 877)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIA Oversize, Box 48, Folder 1196
    - "The Connection: A Play in Two Acts" (Annotated Typescript), 1957 (Box 15, Folder 878)
    - "Le Grand Comedy Theatre: Box Office Statements", Undated (Box 15, Folder 879)
    - Clippings and Jack Gelber's Resume (Photocopy), 1972, 1974, Undated (Box 15, Folder 880)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIA Oversize, Box 48, Folder 1197
    - "The Connection: A Play in Two Acts" (Bound Typescripts), 1957 (Box 15, Folder 881)
    - "The Connection" (Annotated Typescript) and Notes, Undated (Box 15, Folder 882)
    - "The Connection: A Screenplay" (Two Annotated Typescripts) and Notes, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 883)
    - "The Connection, Directed by Shirley Clarke" (Bound Typescript), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 884)
    - "Connecting the Pieces" (Annotated Typescript), Undated (Box 16, Folder 885)
    - Untitled Draft (Annotated Typescript), Undated (Box 16, Folder 886)
    - "A Short Note on 'The Connection'" (Typescript), Undated (Box 16, Folder 887)
    - Small Clippings Album, 1959-1960, Undated (Box 16, Folder 888)
    - "The Connection" (Typescript), Undated (Box 16, Folder 889)
    - "The Connection Revival: Revisions" (Annotated Incomplete Typescript), 1980, Undated (Box 16, Folder 890)
    - "Connection Legal Brief", Undated (Box 16, Folder 891)
      Court of Appeals, State of New York: In the Matter of The Connection Company, Petitioner Respondent, For and Order Pursuant to Article 78 of the Civil Practice Act, against The Regents of the University of the State of New York, Respondents-Appellants, Respondent's Brief by Ephraim London and Martin Garbus, New York: Pandick Press, Inc.
    - Clippings, Advertisements, and Programs, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 892)
    - Clippings, 1960: January (Box 16, Folder 893)
    - Clippings, 1960: February-April (Box 16, Folder 894)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIA Oversize, Box 48, Folder 1198
    - Clippings, Advertisements, and Programs, 1960: May-December (Box 16, Folder 895)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIA Oversize, Box 48, Folder 1199
    - Clippings, Advertisements, and Programs, 1961: January-March (Box 17, Folder 896)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIA Oversize, Box 48, Folder 1200
    - Clippings and Advertisements, 1961: April-December (Box 17, Folder 897)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIA Oversize, Box 48, Folder 1201
    - Clippings and Advertisements, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 898)